■ lazicn378@gmail.com

Pančevo, Serbia

+381/65-368-3833

Profile

I'm a dedicated Full Stack Software Developer, specializing mostly in C#, ASP.NET Core, Javascript, Angular, SQL Databases, Microsoft Azure and I also write some PHP and Laravel code. Currently, I'm on final year on ICT College, Belgrade, Web Programming and Software Engineering department. For the past 4 years I'm actively learning programming, and I have 8 months of professional experience working on enterprise applications. I'm a hardworking person, and I love working in team since I have 4 years of working experience outside of programming. I have finished 4 months internship for specialization in ASP.NET Core Web API with Angular on the front.

I enjoy working collaboratively but can also run with projects independently.

I'm also experienced with software architectures, design patterns and Micorsoft Azure Services.

One thing that I would highlight is that I've been freelancing in my local area for the past 6 months and had success with it.

Currently I'm actively reading software engineering books such as "Head first design patterns" and "Clean Code" so that i keep improving my knowledge in software engineering and development.

Employment History

Full-Stack Software Developer, Cycle d.o.o, Belgrade

September 2022 — Present

- Implemented and updated application modules under the direction of Senior Software Developers.
- Successfully finished tasks based on client requirements.
- Successfully implemented software designs
- Full-stack flow, from UI components, communication with backend, creating backend logic and creating database design for specified problem.
- Using Dapper ORM. Writing a lot of raw SQL queries.
- Using Azure Storage Account, Blob storage and Queues mostly.
- · Working with Git, Azure DevOps, Agile
- Successfully deployed application on Azure and IIS
- Implemented authentication using Auth0 service

Internships

Software Developer, Quadro Consulting, Belgrade

May 2022 — September 2022

Improving Angular and ASP.NET Core skills on 4 months internship. Mostly creating API, calling SQL procedures, using CQRS Pattern, SOLID principles and more.

Education

Skills

C# .NET

ASP.NET

ASP.NET Core

ASP.NET API

JavaScript

Angular 2+

SQL Databases

SQL Server

Entity Framework

Dapper ORM

Microsoft Azure

SOLID

HTML5

CSS3

PHP

Laravel Framework

Bootstrap 4, 5

Angular Material

Agile

Links

Linkedin

GitHub

Languages

Serbian

English

German



ICT College, Belgrade

October 2019 — December 2022

Department for Internet Technologies - Web Programming, software engineering

Courses

C# Intermediate, Udemy

Javascript Intermediate, Udemy

HTL Leonding C# Course (2020/21), Rainer Stropek, YouTube

HTL Leonding Programming Course (2021/22), Rainer Stropek, YouTube